Two years have passed since the War of the Best in Marineford.
Scattered across the world, Luffy and his crew underwent special training to prepare for the trials ahead.
Now they return to the Sabaody Archipelago and move forward to the next stage of their journey, the New World.
The Navy has set out! The Straw Hat's in danger!
The Full Hour of the Week
Three decades ago an arrangement of this 1919 was since claimed the New World Fellowship
It raised nose and 78 cm2 Society to launch the New World.
That happened in the Suyer in European Congress, the New World.
Hi, Sunny.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I hope you aren't lonely.
You're as lovely as ever.
Huh?
Now who is that gorgeous lady?
It's Robin, of course, our super archaeologist!
Boy, did I miss you!
You haven't changed a bit, Frankie.
Is that a joke, sister?
I'm a brand new man!
No, I'm more than a man.
I'm the stuff dreams are made of!
Gaze upon this fantastic transformation, the likes of which this world has never seen!
Yeah, baby!
I'm beyond human comprehension!
Fair enough.
Though I might argue that you've been that way for quite some time now.
Huh?
So I'm not just a freak, I'm a super freak?
Haha!
You're gonna make me blush!
This is the coating, I take it?
It's like jelly.
Yep.
Took a little longer than we expected, but Rayleigh did his part.
Bottom of the sea, here we come!
After everyone gets back, of course.
Speaking of which, I saw Rayleigh at the bar.
Oh yeah?
What number were you?
Who are we missing?
I was number eight.
So the only one left is him.
Hmm.
Oofy.
Well, I'm sure our captain will show him soon enough.
Ship's ready whatever he is.
New weapon's ready too!
That sounds just splendid.
By the way, where's everyone else?
Busy?
Usopp and Sanji stopped by here earlier.
Usopp's picking up some fuel for the trip.
Sanji's getting groceries, of course.
I see.
I ran into something interesting on the way over.
Have you seen these?
Huh?
It's for a concert today.
He's calling himself Soul King.
Yeah, there's a story behind that.
He's big news now.
They're selling his TDs all over the place.
He's left the darkness far behind.
Huh?
He rose up from those foggy seas and now he's a shining star.
His fans raise his name to the heavens, if you'll pardon my poetry.
He didn't say anything about this to me,
but he's making a lot of people happy with his music.
He might not want to be a pirate anymore.
It's the mystery.
Just rock with me.
And you'll see why I'm the king.
Then it's in when you're a skeleton.
Cause calcium is all you need.
Calcium is all you need.
So dish that fat and protein, make your body mean and lean.
Got milk?
My bones are rock and roll and soul is blowing out of my head.
Captain Luffy!
Oh man.
You okay?
Damn it.
Luffy!
Oh my gosh!
I missed you guys so much!
It's me!
Hey Luffy!
Frankie!
Nami!
Sniper King!
Oh wow!
You sure changed a lot in two years, huh?
I bet you're all super strong now!
What are the straw hats up to?
They're just sitting.
Did something happen?
Oh yeah, but keep it down.
They're pissed off so don't look them in the eye.
You don't want to pick a fight with these guys.
What the hell?
Whoa, what happened boss?
I was messed up.
Like all of a sudden I got these chills.
Never seen a trick like that before.
Oh, I forgot.
We got another problem actually.
The thing is, Coco, I mean Robin, isn't a real person.
I'm in the eye.
What the hell?
Oh.
And I'm in the eye.
I was messed up.
Like all of a sudden I got these chills.
Never seen a trick like that before.
Oh, I forgot.
We got another problem, actually.
The thing is, Coco, I mean, Robin is in a real pickle right now.
She was kidnapped?
And you let the bastards go?
Yeah, sorry.
I mean, it all happened so fast.
They must be human traffickers.
This could be real bad.
They could try to sell her at auction.
Like what happened with Kami.
Get a good look, Adam?
No, like I said, it happened all of a sudden.
Hey, Captain, they must have nabbed Coco
because they thought she was the real Robin.
We might be in over our heads here.
I should have known, you're right.
She does look just like the real thing.
Guess that worked against us this time.
Hey, are you keeping secrets from me?
I don't care.
Leave her.
It's not our problem if she dies.
What?
Okay.
Are you nuts?
Luffy, Robin is our friend!
Listen, what is this thing?
And why does it talk?
If this is supposed to be a joke, it's not funny!
We lost Robin once, don't kid about that!
See, it's doing it again.
It can't be a toy.
Take it back, Luffy!
Get off of me!
All right, screw this thing with Robin
and screw this stuffed animal thing.
We've got to get our whole team together here on Crow 46.
And pronto!
That punk with the long nose,
that woman with the orange hair,
and that crappy kid with the giant backpack.
Hunt them down and kick their asses!
We're going to show the whole damn world
what happens when you cross-straw-hat Luffy!
Uh, roger!
Don't kill him yet so we can make a good show of it, huh, Captain?
We'll drag him through the streets
until everyone on Sabo would be shaking in fear.
Works for me!
Are you crazy?
Cut it out!
It's only been two years!
What happened to you?
This is wrong!
I don't know, I'm just...
I'm so sad right now!
You're making me cry!
For the last time!
What is this stupid thing?
If none of you want to help Robin,
nobody's going to say anything!
Why is this runt so attached to us anyway?
When we're done here, maybe we should try selling it.
Damn it, forget this!
I don't have time to argue with you!
I'll save her on my own!
I don't need you!
I'm coming, Robin!
Hold on!
What was that?
They have a fight?
I don't know.
But it's definitely them.
I mean, they haven't aged well in the past two years.
But nobody else has a weird pet like that.
Looks like the reports are true after all.
They're alive.
The Straw Hats are back,
and they're causing trouble again.
This is Grove Number 47.
It's them!
We've sighted six Straw Hats and their pet.
The rumors that they recruited other pirates
seem to be true as well.
They should be assembling on Grove Number 46
any minute now.
Understood.
Then we'd better move quickly.
Evacuate the locals before this becomes a war zone.
Roger.
Pirates are gathering at Grove 46.
Our targets are the Straw Hats.
We'll engage them in the Lawless Zone.
They may have reinforcements.
Block all routes of escape.
Close in on them from Grove 40, 42, and 44.
Make it snappy.
G-1 is sending in backup now.
Center Martin, sir.
I'm heading in first.
PX-5 and PX-7 will accompany me.
Whoa.
You're deploying passive Vistas, sir?
Of course I am.
You fools.
Haven't you learned not to underestimate the Straw Hats?
It's been two years since the war.
Surely they've only grown stronger during that time.
They may be rookies, but make no mistake,
they're the most dangerous pirates here.
As for what happened last time,
we were never able to determine why Kuma sent them away
instead of apprehending them.
But even after his personality was wiped,
his actions seemed to indicate
that they would be returning here someday.
And now that they have,
we must ensure this doesn't end
like it did two years ago.
Let's move!
Counting the
Oh, it's moving.
Must be getting close.
I got plenty more where that came from, buddy boy.
Damn it!
Run for it!
Hmm.
I don't remember so many pirates here last time.
Guess I should put that thing on, huh?
Why don't you stop wasting my time and give me a real discount?
Please don't be angry.
I'm doing my best.
But come on, I can't take 50% off no matter how much you buy.
They're marked out enough already.
Okay, stop.
You can buy clothes when we get to Fishman Island, all right?
We're supposed to buy fuel!
Well, too bad.
We drive a hard bargain.
I'll buy these two, but I want 90% off.
Why me?
Were you learning science these last two years, or just learning how to rip people off?
Hey, Mosshead, keep up.
I don't want you getting lost in the crowd.
If you wander off again, we'll set sail without you.
Yeah?
Then at least I wouldn't be seen with you and your mouth proud.
Hey, I look good.
Something smells nice.
Ooh, I could go for some of that.
Hi.
Well, like what you see?
You bet I do!
A real-life lady with succulent meat!
That bastard, he did run off!
I want to go fishing, but I don't have a fishing pole.
Ooh, look, a fishing store.
Son of a...
Where did he go?
Robin!
Where did they take her?
Damn it!
None of this makes sense!
Why are they acting that way?
Help me!
Zoro!
Nami!
Sanji!
Frankie!
What happened to them?
Why?
Robin gets taken away, and you don't care?
What's wrong with you?
I've been working so hard these past two years
to be a better doctor!
But for what?
Chopper!
Hey!
I can tell it was you from a mile away!
It's you, Sub!
Geez, you got so big!
Just look at you!
I bet I could even ride your back!
Couldn't I?
You doing okay?
Uh-huh!
Oh, so cuddly!
I'm sure the Lady Reindeers just adore you!
I missed you, Chopper!
So much!
Uh...
Nami?
Uh-huh?
Wait a second!
I'm happy to see you guys and all, but now's not the time for this!
Robin is in serious trouble!
Huh?
They're just pretending to be you?
That's why there's tsunamis?
Use your head, okay?
Robin was able to avoid the government for 20 years!
Do you really think someone could just grab her and stuff her in a bag?
No offense, but come on!
I see!
I have a tough time telling humans apart, but...
She didn't even smell right!
Ugh!
Darn it!
Now I'm starting to get mad!
If we see one of them again, I'm gonna punch them in their big, fake face!
They've got some nerve!
Pretending to be us!
I mean, why would they do that in the first place?
I'm gonna punch them in their big, fake face!
They've got some nerve!
I mean, I'm gonna punch them in their big, fake face!
Pretending to be us!
I mean, why would they do that in the first place?
It's almost like we're celebrities or something!
That's crazy!
Hey, don't let it go to your head!
Although, you aren't that far off, since our captain worked up quite a reputation for fighting in that war!
I have to come up with a cool autograph!
I've already got one!
Come on, you two!
We're famous criminals, not celebrities!
Chapa!
Where'd you go?
Come back!
Ah, this sucks!
That little dude was their pet for real!
He, like, doubled our credibility!
Oh, my side hurts!
Are you nuts?!
That talking stuffed animal thing was part of the real straw hats and you let it get away?!
Why didn't you tell me?!
And why aren't you looking for it?!
Oh, sure, go look for it like we have any idea where we went!
Yeah, I mean, Sabaoni is super big and that guy was teeny-tiny! I can't do this! I am done!
Oh, my side hurts!
Are you nuts?!
That talking stuffed animal thing was part of the real straw hats and you let it get away?!
Why didn't you tell me?!
And why aren't you looking for it?!
Oh, sure, go look for it like we have any idea where we went!
Yeah, I mean, Sabaoni is super big and that guy was teeny-tiny! I can't do this! I am dying here!
Forget running! We'll walk! Power walk!
Hancock was right! With all the pirates around, this mustache is pretty handy! I don't want to fight with those guys anyway!
Look, it's that kid with the backpack! Maybe our luck ain't so bad after all!
Boss called him a kid, but he kind of looks like an old man to me!
Oh, it's you guys!
Hey, friend! We need you to come with us!
Let's do this nice and quiet, okay? We don't want any trouble!
You really pissed off our captain, kiddo! I'd prepare for the worst if I was you!
What's wrong? You're so scared you can't even talk?
Hey, Sanji! How's it going?
And Zoro, too! Wow! Long time no see, huh, guys?
Oh, uh-huh! Too long, right?
Yeah, well, let's get going then!
You mean the rest of the crew's here already? Sorry I was so late! Good thing you found me!
Well, he knows the Straw Heads, but we don't know him!
Like I care! Just take him to Luffy and he'll sort this out!
Hmm!
Why are you being such an ass about this? I just want to go fish!
Well, too bad you can't!
Give me one good reason! And while you're at it, give me one good reason why I should even listen to you!
I don't want to hang out together any more than you do, but I can't let you get lost!
Don't get me wrong, though! Nothing would make me happier than leaving you here for good!
Too bad, huh? The point is, everyone's meeting on the ship so you don't get to go fishing on your own!
What a joke!
Number seven thinks he can talk crap to number one and get away with it!
Do you think you're better than me just because you got here first?
It's not like everyone swam to Saba Odi, alright? You got nothing to brag about!
Sure, whatever you say. Number seven.
Fine! You want to fight me? I've trained these legs on the shores of hell for two years!
Then you better use them to run, because I will cut you in half!
diğerה Voyager
Game
Reporting from Grove 46.
All the new recruits the Straw Hats picked up are gathering here, and from the looks of things, I'd say there might be nearly a hundred of them.
Most of them are nobodies, but there are four captains at least.
I see Gashed Albion for one. He's worth $92 million.
Then there's Lib-Serviced Odie, who's worth $88 million.
But those aren't the ones I'm really worried about.
They've also got Wet-Haired Caribou, worth $210 million.
The captain of his crew.
He brought his brother with him. Blood-splattered Koribu. His bounty's at $190 million.
While the Straw Hats continue to gather at the Sunny, the Fake Straw Hats plan a gathering of their own, attracting the attention of the Navy.
As soldiers storm Brooks' concert, the self-styled Soul King is forced to perform his final show.
On the next One Piece, Big Guns Assembled! The Danger of the Fake Straw Hats!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!